Finding Aid for Mary Hunt Papers 1976-2009
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Mary Hunt Papers
1976-2009
1989-2000
Hunt, Mary.
This is a collection of printed materials and photographs collected by Mary Hunt in preparation for writing Hunts' Guides, a series of Michigan travel books.
03164 Aa 2; Ac
18 linear feet
1 oversize folders
Bentley Historical Library University of Michigan
The collection was donated by Mary Hunt (donor no. 8815 ) in 2003. Periodic additions have been received.
The collection is open for research.
A native of Michigan, Mary Hunt was co-founder and co-owner of the Ann Arbor Observer magazine with her husband Don Hunt from July 1976 to 1986. She was also the co-author of Hunts' Guides, a series of Michigan travel books.
This collection contains printed materials and photographs collected by Mary Hunt in preparation for writing the Hunts' Guides series of Michigan travel books. The collection is divided into two series:Printed Materials and Photographs.
Subjects:
Hunt, Mary.; Michigan--Guidebooks.; Tourism--Michigan.; Upper Peninsula (Mich.)--Guidebooks.
Subjects - Visual Material:
Tourism--Michigan.
Genre/Form:
Photographs.; Postcards.
- Printed Materials
  The Printed Materials series consists of visitors' guides, restaurant menus, local maps and brochures about travel attractions, hotels and lodgings, local business and shopping destinations, as well as Hunt's notes on the cities. The files include statewide materials followed by regional, county, and local community. The bulk of this series relates to events and attractions in specific cities.
  - Statewide, 1985-2000; 9 folders (Box 1)
  - Regional, 1883-1999
    - Eastern Michigan, 1988 (Box 1)
    - Mid Michigan (Box 1)
    - Northeastern Michigan (Box 1)
    - Northwestern Michigan, 1991-1998 (Box 1)
    - South Central Michigan (Box 1)
    - Southeastern Michigan, 1983-1999 (Box 1)
    - Southwestern Michigan, 1990-1998 (Box 1)
    - Upper Peninsula, 3 folders (Box 1)
    - West Michigan, 1989-1998 (Box 1)
  - By County, 1985-1996
    - Delta County (Box 1)
    - Genesee County (Box 1)
    - Grand Traverse County, 1987-1991 (Box 1)
    - Harbor County (Box 1)
    - Hillsdale County, 1987 (Box 1)
    - Huron County (Box 1)
    - Isabella County, 1991 (Box 1)
    - Lapeer County (Box 1)
    - Marquette County (Box 1)
    - Midland County, 1985-1991 (Box 1)
    - Oceana County (Box 1)
    - Saginaw County (Box 1)
    - St. Joseph County, 1987-1996 (Box 2)
    - Sanilac County (Box 2)
    - Tuscola County (Box 2)
    - Wayne County (Box 2)
  - Cities (include some earlier items), 1985-2000
    - Acme, circa 1998 (Box 2)
    - Adrian, 1986-2000 (Box 2)
    - Alanson (Box 2)
    - Albion, 1991-1999 (Box 2)
    - Alden (Box 2)
    - Allegan, 1990-1992 (Box 2)
    - Allen, 1988-1996 (Box 2)
    - Allendale, 1998 (Box 2)
    - Alma (Box 2)
    - Almont, 1998 (Box 2)
    - Alpena, circa 1993 (Box 2)
    - Amasa (Box 2)
    - Ann Arbor, 1994-1999; 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Arcadia (Box 2)
    - Atlanta (Box 2)
    - Au Train/Pictured Rocks, circa 1992 (Box 2)
    - Auburn Hills (Box 2)
    - AuGres (Box 2)
    - Augusta, 1990-1999 (Box 2)
    - Bad Axe (Box 2)
    - Baldwin/Idlewild, 1998 (Box 2)
    - Bangor (Box 2)
    - Baraga (Box 2)
    - Barbeau (Box 2)
    - Baroda, 1995-1999 (Box 2)
    - Battle Creek, 1993-1998 (Box 2)
    - Bay City, 1985-1995; 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Bay Harbor, 1997-1999 (Box 2)
    - Bay Port, 1985-1988 (Box 2)
    - Bay View, 1994-1998 (Box 2)
    - Bear Lake (Box 3)
    - Beaver Is, 1993-1999 (Box 3)
    - Belding (Box 3)
    - Bellaire, circa 1998 (Box 3)
    - Belleville, 1998-1999 (Box 3)
    - Belmont (Box 3)
    - Benton Harbor, 1989-1998 (Box 3)
    - Benzonia, circa 1990 (Box 3)
    - Berrien Springs, 1985-1998 (Box 3)
    - Beulah, 1990-1997 (Box 3)
    - Big Bay, 1996-1997 (Box 3)
    - Big Rapids, 1989-1999 (Box 3)
    - Birch Run, 1988-1999 (Box 3)
    - Birmingham, 1989-2000 (Box 3)
    - Black Mountains (Box 3)
    - Black River (Box 3)
    - Blanchard (Box 3)
    - Blissfield (Box 3)
    - Bloomfield Hills, 1987-1999 (Box 3)
    - Boyne, 1994-1999 (Box 3)
    - Breckenridge, circa 1998 (Box 3)
    - Brevort (Box 3)
    - Bridgeport, 1987 (Box 3)
    - Bridgman, 1989-1996 (Box 3)
    - Brighton, 1998-1999 (Box 3)
    - Bronson, 1989-1999 (Box 3)
    - Brooklyn, circa 1999 (Box 3)
    - Brownstown, 1998-1999 (Box 3)
    - Bruce Crossing (Box 3)
    - Buchanan, 1990-1999 (Box 3)
    - Buckley (Box 3)
    - Burdickville (Box 3)
    - Burr Oak, circa 1988 (Box 3)
    - Cadillac, 1985-1990; 2 folders (Box 3)
    - Calumet, circa 1995 (Box 3)
    - Canton (Box 3)
    - Caseville, 1998 (Box 3)
    - Caspian, circa 1997 (Box 3)
    - Cassopolis, 1990-1993 (Box 3)
    - Cedar, 1989-1999 (Box 4)
    - Central Lake, 1992-1995 (Box 4)
    - Centreville, circa 1994 (Box 4)
    - Charlevoix, 1990-1999; 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Charlotte (Box 4)
    - Chassell (Box 4)
    - Cheboygan, 1997-1999 (Box 4)
    - Chelsea, 1986-1997 (Box 4)
    - Chesaning, 1987-1991 (Box 4)
    - Chesterfield (Box 4)
    - Clare, circa 1995-1996 (Box 4)
    - Clement City (Box 4)
    - Clinton, 1988-1996 (Box 4)
    - Clio (Box 4)
    - Climax (Box 4)
    - Clyde (Box 4)
    - Coldwater, 1987-1991 (Box 4)
    - Coloma (Box 4)
    - Colon, 1990-1993 (Box 4)
    - Concord (Box 4)
    - Constantine (Box 4)
    - Copper Harbor, 1995-1996 (Box 4)
    - Crystal Falls, 1994 (Box 4)
    - Crystal Mountain, circa 1997-1999 (Box 4)
    - Curtis/Tahquamenon Falls (Box 4)
    - Dearborn, 1989-1998; 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Decatur, 1997 (Box 4)
    - Delton, 1990 (Box 4)
    - Detroit, 1989-2000; 12 folders (Box 5)
    - Dexter (Box 6)
    - Dorr (Box 6)
    - Douglas, circa 1995 (Box 6)
    - Dowagiac, 1989-1997 (Box 6)
    - Down River, 1996-1997 (Box 6)
    - Drummond Island (Box 6)
    - Dryden (Box 6)
    - Dundee (Box 6)
    - Du, 1995-1996 (Box 6)
    - Eagle Harbor (Box 6)
    - Eagle River (Box 6)
    - East Jordan, 1993-1999 (Box 6)
    - Eaton Rapids (Box 6)
    - Eau Claire, 1990-1998 (Box 6)
    - Edmore, circa 1995 (Box 6)
    - Elderly (Box 6)
    - Elk Rapids, 1996 (Box 6)
    - Elkton (Box 6)
    - Ellsworth (Box 6)
    - Emmett (Box 6)
    - Empire/Sleeping Bear, 1986-1997 (Box 6)
    - Erie (Box 6)
    - Escanaba (Box 6)
    - Evart (Box 6)
    - Fennville, 1992-1993 (Box 6)
    - Fenton (Box 6)
    - Ferndale, 1993 (Box 6)
    - Flat Rock (Box 6)
    - Flint, 1989-1998; 4 folders (Box 6)
    - Fountain/Round Lake (Box 6)
    - Frankenmuth, 1990-1996; 3 folders (Box 6)
    - Frankfort, circa 1992-1998 (Box 7)
    - Freeport (Box 7)
    - Fremont, 1989-1991 (Box 7)
    - Fruitport (Box 7)
    - Gagetown, circa 1998 (Box 7)
    - Galesburg, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Galien (Box 7)
    - Garden (Box 7)
    - Gaylord, circa 1994-1997 (Box 7)
    - Germfask (Box 7)
    - Gladstone (Box 7)
    - Gladwin (Box 7)
    - Glen Arbor, 1990-1999 (Box 7)
    - Gobles, 1997-1998 (Box 7)
    - Goetzville (Box 7)
    - Grand Blanc, 1998 (Box 7)
    - Grand Haven, circa 1993-1999; 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Grand Ledge (Box 7)
    - Grand Rapids, 1990-1999; 3 folders (Box 7)
    - Grand Traverse Village (Box 7)
    - Grant (Box 7)
    - Grass Lake (Box 7)
    - Grayling, circa 1993-1998 (Box 7)
    - Greenville, 1996-1999 (Box 7)
    - Grosse Ile, 1976-1989 (Box 7)
    - Grosse Pointe, 1983-1994 (Box 7)
    - Hamtramck, 1981-1999 (Box 8)
    - Hancock, circa 1997 (Box 8)
    - Hannah (Box 8)
    - Hannahville (Box 8)
    - Hanover, circa 1993 (Box 8)
    - Harbert, 1989-1998 (Box 8)
    - Harbor Beach, circa 1999 (Box 8)
    - Harbor Springs, 1988-1999; 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Harper Woods (Box 8)
    - Harrison, 1990 (Box 8)
    - Harrisville (Box 8)
    - Hart, circa 1992-1998 (Box 8)
    - Hartford, 1988 (Box 8)
    - Hart, 1997 (Box 8)
    - Hartwick Pines, 1996 (Box 8)
    - Hastings, circa 1989-1998 (Box 8)
    - Hickory Corners (Box 8)
    - Higgins Lake (Box 8)
    - Hillman (Box 8)
    - Hillsdale, 1988-1999 (Box 8)
    - Hillside (Box 8)
    - Hol, circa 1990-1999; 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Holly, 1989-1994 (Box 8)
    - Homer (Box 8)
    - Honor/Platte, circa 1995 (Box 8)
    - Hopkins (Box 8)
    - Houghton (Box 8)
    - Houghton Lake (Box 8)
    - Howard City (Box 8)
    - Howell (Box 8)
    - Hudson (Box 8)
    - Indian River, circa 1991-1996 (Box 8)
    - Inland Waterway/Levering, 1998-1999 (Box 8)
    - Interlochen, 1994-1998 (Box 8)
    - Ionia, 1986-1997 (Box 8)
    - Irish Hills, 1985-1998 (Box 8)
    - Iron Mountain, circa 1996 (Box 8)
    - Iron River, circa 1995 (Box 9)
    - Ironwood (Box 9)
    - Ishpeming, 1996-1997 (Box 9)
    - Isle Royale, 1996-1997 (Box 9)
    - Jackson, 1991-1999 (Box 9)
    - Jones, 1988-1997 (Box 9)
    - Jonesville (Box 9)
    - Kalamazoo, 1990-1998; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Kaleva (Box 9)
    - Kalkaska (Box 9)
    - Kazer (Box 9)
    - Kearsage (Box 9)
    - Kewadin (Box 9)
    - Laingsburg (Box 9)
    - Lake City (Box 9)
    - Lake Leelanau, circa 1988-1998 (Box 9)
    - Lake Linden (Box 9)
    - Lake Odessa (Box 9)
    - Lake Orion (Box 9)
    - Lakeport (Box 9)
    - Lakeside, circa 1990-1995 (Box 9)
    - L'Anse/Baraga County (Box 9)
    - Lansing, 1985-1997; 5 folders (Box 9)
    - Lapeer (Box 9)
    - Laurium (Box 9)
    - Lawrence (Box 9)
    - Lawton, 1990 (Box 9)
    - Le, 1985-1999; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Les Cheneaux Islands, circa 1993-1995 (Box 10)
    - Levering (Box 10)
    - Lexington, circa 1997 (Box 10)
    - Litchfield (Box 10)
    - Lowell (Box 10)
    - Ludington, 1994-1998 (Box 10)
    - Mackinac Is, 1991-1999; 3 folders (Box 10)
    - Mackinaw City, 1995-1999; 3 folders (Box 10)
    - Mancelona (Box 10)
    - Manchester (Box 10)
    - Manistee, 1991-1999; 3 folders (Box 10)
    - Manistique, 1994-1995 (Box 10)
    - Maple City (Box 10)
    - Marenisco (Box 10)
    - Marion (Box 10)
    - Marquette, 1996-1997 (Box 10)
    - Marshall, 1996-1999 (Box 10)
    - Martin (Box 10)
    - Mears, 1989-1999 (Box 10)
    - Mendon (Box 11)
    - Menominee (Box 11)
    - Mesick (Box 11)
    - Metamora (Box 11)
    - Michigamme (Box 11)
    - Middleville, circa 1998 (Box 11)
    - Mid, 1993-1999; 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Milford, 1989-1999 (Box 11)
    - Mio (Box 11)
    - Mohawk (Box 11)
    - Monroe, 1989-1998; 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Montague, 1987-1997 (Box 11)
    - Moscow (Box 11)
    - Mottville (Box 11)
    - Mount. Clemens, 1997-1999 (Box 11)
    - Mount Pleasant, 1987-1998 (Box 11)
    - Munising, circa 1996 (Box 11)
    - Muskegon, 1993-2000; 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Nazareth, 1999 (Box 11)
    - Negaunee (Box 11)
    - Newaygo, 1990-1999 (Box 11)
    - Newberry (Box 11)
    - New Baffalo, 1987-1998 (Box 11)
    - New Era (Box 11)
    - New Troy (Box 11)
    - Niles, 1980-1999 (Box 11)
    - North Branch (Box 12)
    - Northport, 1990-1999 (Box 12)
    - Northville (Box 12)
    - Norway/Volcan (Box 12)
    - Nunica, 1996 (Box 12)
    - Oak Park, 1993 (Box 12)
    - Oden (Box 12)
    - Okemos, 1989-1994 (Box 12)
    - Omena, circa 1998 (Box 12)
    - Omer (Box 12)
    - Onaway (Box 12)
    - Onekama, 1999 (Box 12)
    - Ontonagon (Box 12)
    - Oscoda, 1992-1998 (Box 12)
    - Ossineke (Box 12)
    - Ottawa and Nicolet National Forest, circa 1994 (Box 12)
    - Otsego (Box 12)
    - Owosso (Box 12)
    - Paradise, circa 1995 (Box 12)
    - Paw Paw, 1986-1999 (Box 12)
    - Pentwater, 1998 (Box 12)
    - Petersburg (Box 12)
    - Petoskey, 1991-1999; 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Pigeon (Box 12)
    - Pinconning (Box 12)
    - Plainwell (Box 12)
    - Plymouth, 1989-1990 (Box 12)
    - Pontiac, 1989-1998 (Box 12)
    - Porcupine Mountains (Box 12)
    - Portage, 1998 (Box 12)
    - Port Austin, 1999-2000 (Box 12)
    - Port Hope (Box 12)
    - Port Huron, 1987-1988 (Box 12)
    - Port Sanilac (Box 12)
    - Prairieville, 1986-1989 (Box 12)
    - Presque Isle (Box 12)
    - Rapid River (Box 12)
    - Richland (Box 12)
    - Rochester (Box 12)
    - Rockford, 1988-1995 (Box 12)
    - Rogers City (Box 12)
    - Romeo, 1998 (Box 12)
    - Roscommon (Box 12)
    - Rothbury, 1994-1995 (Box 12)
    - Royal Oak, 1988-1990 (Box 12)
    - Saginaw, 1989-1998; 3 folders (Box 13)
    - St. Clair Flats, circa 1996 (Box 13)
    - St. Ignace, 1990-1997 (Box 13)
    - St. Johns, 1985-1987 (Box 13)
    - St. Joseph, 1986-1996; 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Sandusky (Box 13)
    - Saugatuck/Douglas, 1990-1999; 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Sault Ste. Marie, 1988-1997 (Box 13)
    - Schwartz Creek (Box 13)
    - Scotts, 1994 (Box 13)
    - Scottville/Crystal Lake (Box 13)
    - Seney (Box 13)
    - Shelby, circa 1999 (Box 13)
    - Silver City (Box 13)
    - Skanee, circa 1996 (Box 13)
    - Sleeping Bear Dunes, 1991-1999 (Box 13)
    - Sodus, circa 1989 (Box 13)
    - South Haven, 1986-1998; 2 folders (Box 13)
    - South Lyon (Box 13)
    - Stanton, 1990 (Box 13)
    - Stevensville, 1989-1995 (Box 13)
    - Stockbridge (Box 13)
    - Sturgis, 1987-1991 (Box 13)
    - Sutton's Bay, 1985-1999 (Box 14)
    - Tawas, 1994-1997 (Box 14)
    - Taylor (Box 14)
    - Tecumseh (Box 14)
    - Thompsonville, 1990-1993 (Box 14)
    - Three Oaks, 1991-1999 (Box 14)
    - Three Rivers, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Tipton, 1988-1997 (Box 14)
    - Torch Lake, 1999 (Box 14)
    - Traverse City, 1992-1999; 4 folders (Box 14)
    - Troy, 1987-1989 (Box 14)
    - Twin Lake, 1996-1998 (Box 14)
    - Union City (Box 14)
    - Union Pier, 1986-1998 (Box 14)
    - Vassar (Box 14)
    - Vermontville (Box 14)
    - Vicksburg, circa 1998 (Box 14)
    - Wakefield (Box 14)
    - Walled Lake (Box 14)
    - Walloon Lake (Box 14)
    - Warren Dunes, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Washington (Box 14)
    - Watersedge, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Watersmeet/Sylvania, 1994-1996 (Box 14)
    - Watervliet (Box 14)
    - Wellston, 1996 (Box 14)
    - West Bloomfield, 1996 (Box 14)
    - West Branch/Ogemaw County, 1995 (Box 14)
    - Wetmore (Box 14)
    - White Cloud, 1988-1998 (Box 14)
    - Whitefish Point (Box 14)
    - Whitehall/White Lake, 1989-1998 (Box 14)
    - White Pigeon (Box 14)
    - White Pine (Box 14)
    - Wilderness State Park (Box 14)
    - Williamsburg (Box 14)
    - Williamston (Box 14)
    - Willow Run, circa 1987 (Box 14)
    - Wolverine (Box 14)
    - Ypsilanti, 1985-1998 (Box 14)
    - Zee, circa 1994 (Box 14)
  - Other published materials, including some topical subdivisions, dated to, 2009
    - Albion (Box 15)
    - Alger County (Box 15)
    - Allegan (Box 15)
    - Ann Arbor (Box 15)
    - Baraga (Box 15)
    - Battle Creek (Box 15)
    - Bicyclists (Box 15)
    - Big Rapids (Box 15)
    - Bloomfield Hills (Box 15)
    - Boating (Box 15)
    - Calumet (Box 15)
    - Campgrounds (Box 15)
    - Cassopolis (Box 15)
    - Central Upper Peninsula, 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Cheboygan (Box 15)
    - Copper Country (Box 15)
    - Copper Harbor (Box 15)
    - Curtis (Box 15)
    - Dearborn (Box 15)
    - Detroit (Box 15)
    - Detroit Area (Box 15)
    - Douglas (Box 15)
    - Drummond Island (Box 15)
    - Eastern Michigan (Box 15)
    - Eastern Upper Peninsula (Box 15)
    - Emmet County (Box 15)
    - Flint (Box 15)
    - Grand Haven (Box 15)
    - Grand Rapids
      - General, 2 folders (Box 15)
      - Furniture (Box 15)
      - Menus (Box 15)
    - Grayling (Box 15)
    - Hancock (Box 15)
    - Harbor Springs (Box 15)
    - Holland (Box 15)
    - Isle Royale (Box 15)
    - Jackson (Box 15)
    - Kalamazoo (Box 15)
    - Keweenaw (Box 15)
    - Lake Gogebic Times (Box 15)
    - Lake Superior (Box 15)
    - L'Anse (Box 15)
    - Lansing, 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Lenawee County (Box 15)
    - Ludington (Box 15)
    - Mackinac Island (Box 15)
    - Mackinaw City (Box 15)
    - Manistee (Box 15)
    - Marquette County (Box 15)
    - Menus (Box 16)
      (see also oversize folder)
    - Michigan (Box 16)
    - Michigan Beer (Box 16)
    - Michigan Travel (Box 16)
    - Mid Michigan (Box 16)
    - Monroe County (Box 16)
    - Munising (Box 16)
    - Muskegon (Box 16)
    - Natural Resources, Dept. of (DNR) (Box 16)
    - Neebish Island (Box 16)
    - Newberry (Box 16)
    - Northern Michigan, Restaurant Guide (Box 16)
    - Owosso (Box 16)
    - Petoskey (Box 16)
    - Railroad (Box 16)
    - Royal Oak (Box 16)
    - Saginaw (Box 16)
    - St. Ignace (Box 16)
    - St. Joseph (Box 16)
    - Saugatuck (Box 16)
    - Sault Ste. Marie (Box 16)
    - SEVA Foundation (Box 16)
    - Ski (Box 16)
    - Snowmobile (Box 16)
    - South Haven (Box 16)
    - Spring Lake/Fruitport (Box 16)
    - Tahquamenon Area (Box 16)
    - Three Rivers (Box 16)
    - Trout Lake (Box 16)
    - Upper Peninsula (Box 16)
    - Upper Western Michigan (Box 16)
    - Van Buren County (Box 16)
    - Washtenaw County (Box 16)
    - Western Michigan (Box 16)
    - Western Upper Peninsula (Box 16)
    - Zeeland, Furniture (Box 16)
- Photographs
  The Photographs series consists of photographs, postcards, slides and negatives, arranged alphabetically by city name. Photos that have some information but not enough to identify cities are separately arranged in the Michigan Miscellaneous.
  - Mainly with some earlier dated images, 1991-1997
    - Acme (Box 17)
    - Albion (Box 17)
    - Allegan (Box 17)
    - Ann Arbor (Box 17)
    - Arcadia, 1995 (Box 17)
    - Au Train/Munising/Pictured Rocks, circa 1995-1996 (Box 17)
    - Baldwin (Box 17)
    - Battle Creek (Box 17)
    - Bay Port, 1995 (Box 17)
    - Bay View (Box 17)
    - Benton Harbor (Box 17)
    - Beulah, 1995 (Box 17)
    - Calumet, 1996 (Box 17)
    - Caro, 1995 (Box 17)
    - Caspian, 1995 (Box 17)
    - Cedar (Box 17)
    - Cedarville, 1995 (Box 17)
    - Cheboygan, 1995 (Box 17)
    - Chelsea (Box 17)
    - Colon (Box 17)
    - Cook Nuclear Plant (Box 17)
    - Copper Harbor (Box 17)
    - Cranbrook (Box 17)
    - Cross Village, 1995 (Box 17)
    - Delton, circa 1985-1986 (Box 17)
    - Detroit, 1989-1998 (Box 17)
    - Drummond Is, 1995 (Box 17)
    - Dundee (Box 17)
    - Eagle Harbor (Box 17)
    - Eau Claire (Box 17)
    - Edmore (Box 17)
    - Elk Rapids, 1995 (Box 17)
    - Fenton, 1976 (Box 17)
    - Flint (Box 17)
    - Frankenmuth, 1991-1993 (Box 17)
    - Frankfort, 1995 (Box 17)
    - Glen Arbor, 1995 (Box 17)
    - Grand Haven (Box 17)
    - Grand Rapids (Box 17)
    - Gregory, 1992 (Box 17)
    - Grindstone City, 1994-1995 (Box 17)
    - Harbor Springs, 1995 (Box 17)
    - Hessel, 1995 (Box 17)
    - Hillsdale (Box 17)
    - Holland (Box 17)
    - Homer (Box 17)
    - Houghton, circa 1996 (Box 17)
    - Huron (Box 17)
    - Interlochen, 1995 (Box 17)
    - Irish Hills (Box 17)
    - Iron River/Land O'Lakes, 1996 (Box 17)
    - Isle Royale (Box 17)
    - Jacobsville (Box 17)
    - Kalamazoo (Box 17)
    - Keweenaw, circa 1990-1996 (Box 17)
    - Lake Leelanau (Box 17)
    - Lake Linden (Box 17)
    - Lansing (Box 17)
    - Les Cheneaux, 1995 (Box 17)
    - Ludington, circa 1989-1994 (Box 17)
    - Mackinac Is, 1995 (Box 17)
    - Mackinaw City, 1995 (Box 17)
    - Manchester (Box 17)
    - Marquette (Box 17)
    - Mears (Box 17)
    - Menominee Range, circa 1995-1996 (Box 17)
    - Mesick, 1995 (Box 17)
    - Mid, 1992 (Box 17)
    - Milan (Box 17)
    - Mohawk, 1996 (Box 17)
    - Montague (Box 17)
    - Muskegon (Box 17)
    - Negaunee (Box 17)
    - New Buffalo (Box 17)
    - Norway (Box 17)
    - Owosso (Box 17)
    - Paw Paw (Box 17)
    - Petoskey (Box 17)
    - Porcupine Mountains (Box 17)
    - Port Austin, 1995 (Box 17)
    - Port Sanilac (Box 17)
    - Portage, 1995 (Box 17)
    - Presque Isle, 1993-1996 (Box 17)
    - Rochester (Box 17)
    - Rockford (Box 17)
    - Royal Oak (Box 17)
    - St. Joseph (Box 17)
    - Saginaw (Box 17)
    - Saugatuck (Box 17)
    - Seney/Tahquamenon Falls, 1995-1997 (Box 17)
    - Sleeping Bear National Lakeshore, 1995 (Box 17)
    - South Haven (Box 17)
    - Straits Area, circa 1997 (Box 17)
    - Sutton's Bay (Box 17)
    - Traverse City (Box 17)
    - Wakefield (Box 17)
    - Watersmeet/Sylvania, 1996 (Box 17)
    - White Cloud (Box 17)
    - White Lake (Box 17)
    - White Pigeon (Box 17)
    - White Pine (Box 17)
    - Whitefish Point and the Soo, 1993-1996 (Box 17)
    - Whitehall (Box 17)
    - Ypsilanti, 1992 (Box 17)
    - Michigan Misc. (Box 17)
    - Negatives (Box 17)
  - Mainly with some earlier, 1998-1999
    (The descriptions were made by Mary Hunt)
    - Adrian, 2 envelopes (Box 18)
    - Afrah Pastries, 1990 (Box 18)
    - Albion Background (Box 18)
    - Alpena, G. R. Bronson Park, Kalamazoo, July 1998 (Box 18)
    - Ann Arbor, 1964 (Box 18)
    - Battle Creek SW, 1999 (Box 18)
    - Bay City, Durand, Frankenmuth, etc. (Box 18)
    - Bay Harbor Straits (Box 18)
    - Bay Harbor Straits, Krupp's-Flint (Box 18)
    - Beaver Island, Hamtramck, etc. (Box 18)
    - Benton Harbor Arts Walk, October, 1998 (Box 18)
    - Borders Book Shop, Ann Arbor (Box 18)
    - Bowers Harbor, Willard Hilton (Box 18)
    - Charlevoix Levering, Carp Lake, Frederic (Box 18)
    - Cheboygan, Ocqueoc (Box 18)
    - Dearborn Arab Festival, 1999 (Box 18)
    - Dearborn, Arab, Metro, June 1999 (Box 18)
    - Detroit Bakeries, Oakwood, Gwen Organic (Box 18)
    - Detroit, Hamtramck, Metro, 1999 (Box 18)
    - Detroit, Labor Day Tyree (Box 18)
    - Detroit-SW, Adventist Museum, Dewey, Jesse Hickman, August / September 1999 (Box 18)
    - Dowagiac/St. Louis (Box 18)
    - Eastern Market, Crossroads Village, September 1995 (Box 18)
    - Eaton Rapids Island Park, Midland School (Box 18)
    - Elberta, Car Ferry, July 1999 (Box 18)
    - Flint, Uncle Bob's Diner (Box 18)
    - Gaylord, Mackinaw Straits (Box 18)
    - Grand Haven (Box 18)
    - Grand Rapids, Newaygo (Box 18)
    - Hamtramck, Ann Arbor (Box 18)
    - Hamtramck, Detroit, September 1998 (Box 18)
    - Harbor Beach, Huron City, Concord (Box 18)
    - Harbor Country, Detroit, SW, 1998 (Box 18)
    - Holland, Battle Creek, Kalamazoo, October 1998 (Box 18)
    - IXL (Box 18)
    - Jackson, Flint (Box 18)
    - Kaleva, Onekama, Northport, Glen Arbor, July 1999 (Box 18)
    - Leelanau, Northport, Suzanne W. (Box 18)
    - Ludington, Interlochen (Box 18)
    - Ludington, NW, 1999 (Box 18)
    - Ludington/Tustin, July 1999 (Box 18)
    - Ludington State Park NW (Box 18)
    - Mackinac/Grand Hotel, CCC Camp, Dowagiac: Heddon, Mendon: 2 girls, June 1998 (Box 18)
    - Mackinac Island, Cheboygan, June 1998 (Box 18)
    - Macomb Pumpkins, Marine City, Raven & Richard, October 1998 (Box 18)
    - Manitowoc, Keweenaw/Duffy, Marquette-totems, August 1999 (Box 18)
    - Marcia, Bruce, March 1999 (Box 18)
    - Marine City, Harsens Is, October 1998 (Box 18)
    - Marquette Totem Pole, Mackinaw, Levering (Box 18)
    - Marshall, Local Stuff, Fermi 2 Monroe (Box 18)
    - Mattawan: Adeline & Sonora, Detroit Cultural Center Festival, September 1998 (Box 18)
    - Matthaei, Outside Orlando, September 1999 (Box 18)
    - Muskegon (Box 18)
    - Muskegon Farmers Market, 1958 (Box 18)
    - Muskegon, Holland (Box 18)
    - Muskegon, Holland, Nettie Bay, Rogers City, March-May 1999 (Box 18)
    - New Buffalo, St. Joe SW (Box 18)
    - Petoskey, Beaver Island, Tree-Mendous Fruit (Eau Clair, MI), October 1995 (Box 18)
    - Plymouth, Milford, Sam (Box 18)
    - Port Huron, October 1998 (Box 18)
    - Port Sanilac (Box 18)
    - Port Sanilac, Hastings, Delton, Kalamazoo (Box 18)
    - Posen Area, NC/NE (Box 18)
    - Rogers City, September 1998 (Box 18)
    - Rogers City/Presque Isle (Box 18)
    - Saginaw, Bruce Crudup, January 1999 (Box 18)
    - Saginaw, Montague Inn (Box 18)
    - Saginaw, St. Mary's, Mexican Restaurant, Bay City Polish Church, January 1999 (Box 18)
    - Sarkozy Bakery, Braeloch Herb & Garden Farm, Alpen Rose Restaurant (Box 18)
    - Saugatuck, Spring 1995 (Box 18)
    - Sleeping Bear Presentation (Box 18)
    - Sylva, Sylvania, Iron River, October 1996 (Box 18)
    - Thumb, September 1999 (Box 18)
    - Thumb, Caseville Side, September 1999 (Box 18)